Oh, gosh, I can do one in about 10 or 15 minutes max.
I mean, it's that easy. It's just quick and easy.
So your annotated maps are incredible.
They're very easy to use, user-friendly, and they're quick.
But now that you have the tool where we can go in and just click in there
and just add what we need or delete or make some changes,
it is seamless and very easy.
And I've really enjoyed that tool.
And then I can follow the progress.
For me, I've got my week's worth of work I want to get done that week,
and it helps me keep track of that.
And as we do it, I can close it out as construction complete, needing splicing,
and then I'll assign a splicer for that, so it drops in their queue,
but I'm still able to monitor at the same time.
So I know it's a great tool. It's very clean, very easy, user-friendly.
Everybody should take a look at it, in my personal opinion.